

BRILEATHERMAN

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

bleathel.wixsite.com/myportfolio

(330) 690-8446

bleathel@kent.edu

I am currently a student at Kent State University working toward my degree in Visual Communication Design. I have worked with our University Athletics Marketing department for over I year producing promotional content and social media graphics. I am dedicated to my work and a creative problem solver.

Education

Bachelor of Fine Arts Kent State University

Cumulative GPA 3.34
Visual Communication Design Major
User Experience Minor

Awards

Deans List

Spring 2015-Current Awarded to students obtaining a 3.4 GPA or above in a semester.

Trustee Scholarship

Fall 2015-Current Awarded to students obtaining a 2.5 GPA or above in a semester.

Skills

Adobe InDesign
Adobe Photoshop
Adobe Illustrator
Microsoft Powerpoint
Microsoft Word
Adobe After Effects

Work Experience

Kent State University

Student Graphic Designer Jan. 2018-Current

- Create and design all ranges of promotional items for the athletic department.
- Work with team to produce fliers, badges, posters, and t-shirt designs

American Eagle Outfitters

Sales Associate Nov. 2017-Feb. 2018

- Assisted team members when necessary in handling registers, organizing inventory, and unloading merchandise
- Processed customer transactions
- Helped to create unique displays that attract customers

Valley Cafe

Server May 2015-Jan. 2018

- Delivered exceptional, friendly, and fast service.
- Answered customer inquiries and resolved issues promptly
- Assisted in training of new staff

Leadership

New Member Educator

Phi Mu Fraternity Spring 2016-Spring 2017

- Educated incoming new members about key fraternal history and values.
- Provided a safe and productive environment for new members
- Educated new members in time management and financial skills as well as healthy living and social skills.

President

Phi Mu Fraternity Spring 2017-Spring 2018

- Managed an executive board of 13 members to oversee and facilitate 180 members.
- Presided over chapter and officer meetings using parliamentary procedure.
- Delegated tasks to fellow executive board members in order to encourage participation.
- Fostered an environment that promotes teamwork and inclusivity.
- Acted as main point of contract for any inquiries from the University, media sources, headquarters, and philanthropic companies